## **CLARA KANG: WEB DEVELOPER**

213-335-0214 | clara.kang91@gmail.com | clarakang.com | linkedin.com/in/clarakang | github.com/claarafy

#### **SUMMARY**

I'm a web developer with experience in marketing and mathematics educational background. A mathematical approach to web development helped me get a good grasp of the back-end development, and creativity in product decision and front-end UI experience. Currently, I'm working with MERN stack application project and developing my knowledge in React, as well as solidifying my foundation in the languages I learned.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | jQuery | Ruby | Rails | Node.js | Express | React | ES6 | AJAX | Wordpress | SaSS | Bootstrap | P5 | PostgreSQL | mongoDB | Authentication with bcrypt/passport/jwt | Git/Github | Heroku

#### **PROJECTS**

NO LALA LAND May 2017

NO LALA LAND is a single-page map application that provides street parking information in vicinity of the queried location.

React with ES6 | Node.js | Express | MongoDB | HTML | CSS | Mapbox (3<sup>rd</sup> Party API)

**Ctrl + F** May 2017

Ctrl + F is a search engine application that allows both searching and reviewing on the specific result; users are able to see the search result with appended reviews on the website all in one space.

Node.js | Express | MongoDB | HTML | CSS | Bing (3<sup>rd</sup> Party API)

Until We Part April 2017

*Until We Part* is a photo-sharing web application for private groups, particularly built for families. Ruby on Rails | Bootstrap | HTML | CSS

**U-B-U** April 2017

*U-B-U (You Be You)* is a 2-player paper doll memory game with custom-drawn character. JavaScript | jQuery | CSS | HTML

## **EXPERIENCE**

### Marketing Manager, Tapzin Korea

February 2015 – August 2015

- Led a team of six to curate engaging magazine articles to create Tapzin's own contents. Targeted curation has resulted in 5% increase in monthly downloads as well as 2% growth of Monthly Active Users.
- Raised brand awareness by developing online campaigns on SNS channels, by communicating with the partners (magazine and media companies), for collaborative promotion projects and event coordination.

# **Accounting Assurance** Intern, PwC Korea

June 2013 – August 2013

• Worked with a team of audits to conduct "test of detail," research, as well as evaluation of current conditions for the largest telecommunication company in Korea.

### **EDUCATION**

Emory University August 2010 — May 2014

Bachelor of Arts(B.A.), Joint Major in Economics and Mathematics

General Assembly March 2017 — May 2017

Web Development Immersive: Front-end / Back-end Web Development